♪♪
Zero!
And now, America's
favorite game show,
where right answers times
quick thinking means big money.
It's time for...
Starring Mr. Apple Pie himself,
America's number
1 game show host,
the man with all the
questions... Dennis Blake.
Also starring America's
number 1 clock watcher,
the woman with America's favorite
smile... The one and only Kari Summers.
Tonight's show is the fifth
and final from New York City.
Next week, we'll be coming to
you live from Atlanta, Georgia.
And now, here they are!
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
Our contestants are ready, so
here is tonight's first question.
In England's War of the Roses,
what color were the roses?
- Walter, it's you.
- Red and white.
Red and white is
correct for $800.
Moving right on,
what was French revolutionary
leader Jean-Paul Marat doing
when he was murdered?
Walter?
Taking a bath.
Taking a bath is also
correct for another $800.
Change of pace question...
Who, after Joe DiMaggio, had the
longest hitting streak in baseball?
Ted Williams.
Look at that. Look at
that. I stumped them.
- I got it in one second.
- It was Pete Rose.
Oh, I'm sorry.
We're out of time.
No baseball fans here today.
Pete Rose was
the correct answer.
Hmm.
- And here's tonight's...
- You say she's coming to Atlanta?
Yeah. The whole show
is. It tours the country.
They'll be here for two
weeks starting next Tuesday.
There are two-and-a-half angels
mentioned by name in the Bible.
Who is the half angel?
Lucifer.
Lucifer is correct
for another $800.
- Huh.
- How did you know that?
- Hmm? I don't know. I just know.
- You're our daily winner,
which means that once again Kari is
going to lead you to the winner's circle,
where you will try to answer
tonight's final countdown question.
Kari?
She does that very
well, too, doesn't she?
Mm-hmm.
Remember that for each full
second remaining on the clock,
you will receive $1,000.
- Are you ready?
- I'm ready.
All right, then,
let's get right at
tonight's final question
on It's About Time.
- Ben...
- Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Whose face is pictured
on the $100,000 bill?
Trick question...
there is no bill.
Woodrow Wilson.
Woodrow Wilson?
Woodrow Wilson
is absolutely correct.
There is such a bill.
They're just not circulated.
- You've won $8,000.
- Ooh.
Which gives you a
grand total of $86,000.
That also means you're
going to be back tomorrow night
to square off against
two new contestants.
I'll bet she is just a nice,
down-to-earth all-American girl.
And we want you back, too.
That's it for tonight, folks.
Put the apple pie in the
oven, Mom. I'm coming home.
Transportation assistance
for It's About Time
has been provided by
TransGlobal Airlines.
While in New York, accommodations
for the It's About Time cast and crew
There... Marjorie Wood,
Talent Coordinator.
Said she could get me as many
tickets to the show as I want.
- You still want to?
- Yeah. Probably,
she can get you backstage
to meet Kari Summers,
and Marge could probably
get you on the show.
No, thanks. On national
TV I'd probably choke.
Come on, let's get back to work.
Do you think Kari
Summers is her real name?
It's about fun for
the whole family.
Hey, sorry I'm late.
I just got these from the
Chamber of Commerce.
Oh, not more apples.
Everybody in the country
thinks that apples are my thing.
What can I say?
Dig in.
Oh, sorry. I didn't
mean to interrupt.
You didn't interrupt,
Dennis. I was waiting for you.
People, I just flew in from Chicago,
and Globe Syndication is not happy.
It seems the number-crunchers have detected
a disturbing pattern in the ratings
in a dozen or so of
the major markets.
They are slowly
but surely slipping.
They told me to do whatever
it takes to nip this in the bud.
Marge, sweetheart, thousands of people
want to be It's About Time contestants.
Am I right? Babe,
tens of thousands.
Hundreds of thousands.
In fact, whenever we have interviews,
there's a line going around the building.
- Am I right?
- Yes.
Well?
With all those people to choose from,
how come our contestants always look
like they crawled out of the
basement of the public library?
How come a few good-looking blondes
can't make the cut from time to time?
Oh, come on, Larry. This is a
game show, not a beauty pageant.
From now on, I want at least one serving
of cheesecake and/or beefcake per show.
You got me, babe?
Yeah, I got you, Larry.
Norman.
Norman, Norman, Norman.
My brother.
My dear baby brother.
Close-ups of people thinking
are like watching paint dry.
Don't think of yourself
as a game show director.
Imagine you're doing
music videos, huh?
Crazy angles, quick cuts,
smash pan, big zooms.
Keep it going...
boom, boom, boom.
You're the MTV generation,
kiddo. Make it work for you, huh?
Whatever you say, Larry.
Yeah.
Kari, love of my life.
Lower necklines
and higher hemlines.
Bingo.
And last but not least,
Dennis, our erstwhile host.
What does erstwhile mean?
It means I'm replacing you,
babe, with him: Lance McCormick.
He's young. He's hip.
He's you 15 years ago.
Friday's your last
gig, babe. Sorry.
Try not to take it personally.
Okay, people, that's it.
I'll see you Friday
at the next taping.
I can't believe you're
doing this to me.
After all this time,
aren't you even...
If you knew what
I've been through...
Hi, Kari.
Is everything okay?
What Larry did to you
today was really awful.
I'm trying to talk him into
reconsidering, but I'm not getting too far.
Can I see him?
- Larry?
- Hmm.
Dennis is here.
Good luck.
Thanks anyway.
You're a good friend.
Hi.
Can we talk for a minute?
I'm going to go for a walk.
What?
I, uh...
just got offered a job as a
host on the new talk show in L.A.
That's great.
Well, I wanted to talk to you
about it first before I took it
because I know you've got
a new show in the hopper...
Who told you that?
Norm, I guess.
Well, anyway, I figured
you'd need a familiar face
to help get this
thing off the ground,
and if I took the job I could be tied up
for years, and we go back a long way,
so I figured that I would
give you first crack at moi.
I don't need you, Dennis.
Damn it, Larry. How
can you do this to me?
I have worked for
you for 12 years.
How can you just throw
me to the wolves like this?
I'm a businessman, Dennis.
You used to be good for
business. Now you're not.
I thought we were friends.
I don't do friends.
And now, to the final
question in our $100 round...
Camera 3, start a slow
zoom in on Dennis. That's it.
Camera 1, zoom on contestants.
It's you, Walter.
The sandwich.
The sandwich is correct.
All right, contestants, here is
the final question in this round.
Be right there.
Scientists have divided the natural
world into how many kingdoms?
Walter for $700.
- Three?
- Yes.
Three is correct.
Now, Walter
you've done it again.
For the 22nd day in a row, you
have become our daily winner,
which means that you will be in
our final countdown one more time.
Kari, will you escort Walter
to the winner's circle, please?
And that's a cut.
Lose the other contestants and
set up the final countdown area.
Standard operating
procedure, folks.
We always do a little restaging
before the final countdown.
Oh.
However, thanks to the miracle of editing,
you never see that on your sets at home.
Hold on. People,
please, stay in your seats.
We'll have this
fixed in a minute.
- Charlie?
- Everything's down.
Charlie, what the hell's
going on down there?
- Charlie?
- He's gone, too.
Aah!
Okay, people.
Look, I don't know what happened,
but it looks like we're back in business.
Charlie, we'll roll tape as
soon as you give me the word.
All right, everybody, stand by.
- Quiet, please.
- All right, Walter, here we go.
Your final countdown
question for the night is:
Experiments with liquid helium
by the Dutch physicist Onnes
produced a breakthrough in
what area of modern medicine?
Cryogenics.
Cryogenics...
is correct for $6,000, which
brings your grand total to $98,000.
That's all the time
we have, folks.
So tune in tomorrow to find out
just how far Walter here can go.
That's your cue, Mom.
Get the apple pie in the
oven, please. I'm coming home.
Conrad McMasters.
How are you?
Come here. Let me look at you.
You look good.
Well, you haven't exactly turned
into a fat, ugly slob yourself.
Thank you.
Oh, you must be Ben Matlock.
- Yeah.
- Hi. I'm Marjorie Wood.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi.
So Conrad's your investigator.
Well, he always
was pretty nosey.
Hey, would it be okay for
Ben to meet Kari Summers?
Oh, that's not really necessary.
What is it?
Oh, dear God.
Well, Bob.
Ben, what are you doing here? I
haven't even arrested anybody yet.
We just came to see the show.
Ahem.
Does anybody recognize this?
Why, it's... mine.
My apple peeler.
We found it behind a curtain
backstage just a few minutes ago.
Last time I saw it, it
was in my dressing room.
You're Dennis Blake, aren't you?
Yeah.
My wife's a big fan of yours.
That's nice.
In fact, she was a
little upset this morning.
She heard on some talk show
that you had just been fired.
That true?
Yeah.
Who fired you, Mr. Blake?
Well, the executive
producer, Larry Fisher.
But I'm...
Maybe we should continue
this discussion downtown.
This is a mistake.
Mr. Matlock,
Dennis is no killer.
Please, you've got to help him.
- Well, I don't know.
- No, please.
He can pay your
fee... oh, easily.
He makes a pretty good wage?
And he's innocent.
Dennis is the most
gentle man I know.
Uh, this apple pie and Mom thing,
does he say that after every show?
He has for 15 years.
Hey, Bob, wait a minute.
Maybe I'll bum a
ride downtown, huh?
- They look much better short.
- Yeah?
Oh, they're great.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm happy to announce
that there is life after Larry.
Everybody in this room is still employed,
and It's About Time is still in production.
What are you? Alexander Haig?
You've got it, babe.
I'm in charge now.
It's About Time belongs to me.
It's part of my
brother's estate.
And, before any of you wonders
what Dennis is doing here,
he's here because
I want him here.
Now, getting down to business.
Item number 1: It's
About Time questions.
The police have agreed to remove them
from Larry's office and give them to me.
Then, at least, that way, we won't
have to be shelling out a small fortune
to the research company
for at least another month.
Item number 2: The Denster.
Not only did I bail him
out, but I un-fired him.
He's back in the
saddle for good.
Welcome back, Dennis.
See? What did I tell
you? They love you, babe.
Nobody could believe it.
I mean, this guy had become a clone
of his brother practically overnight.
You going to have trouble
taking orders from him?
Nah.
Norm can't be any
worse than Larry was.
What's the matter?
Marge, I've got to ask
you some questions.
Go ahead.
Ben and I figure that whoever really
killed Larry was someone on the show.
There's just no other explanation
for the blackout and that peeler.
Yeah. That makes sense.
Which means we need to find out
who else on the show had a motive.
Am I a suspect?
Dennis says a friend of yours
used to work on the show.
Todd Delquist?
And I'm sure that
Dennis has told you
that he was considerably
more than a friend.
He says Larry fired him.
That was quite a few
months ago, Conrad.
He says it made it impossible for
him to find work on another show.
That was the rumor.
Dennis seems to think that what
happened to your ex-boyfriend
had something to do with you.
Larry kept propositioning me.
I kept refusing.
So instead of firing
me, he fires Todd.
The only other job
Todd could get was this
job at a radio station
down in Boise, Idaho.
Larry did all that just
to get back at you?
Being a vindictive
SOB was his life.
How could you work for somebody
like that? Why didn't you just quit?
I didn't realize it was so
late. I've got to get going.
You were afraid if you quit, he'd
blacklist you, too, weren't you?
I would have taken
him to court, Conrad.
It would have been a lot more
satisfying taking his money than his life.
Hello, everyone.
Please take your seats.
Hi, I'm Marjorie Wood.
I'm the talent coordinator
for It's About Time.
The good news is that all 20 of you
have passed our preliminary screening
and have met our
eligibility requirement.
The bad news is
that not all of you
will actually become It's
About Time contestants.
I'm going to meet with two
other groups just like this one,
and we're going to
split you into trios,
and then we're going
to see how well you do
in a mock game
of It's About Time,
shortly after which you will be notified
whether or not you've made the cut.
Now, Michael.
Now I'm going to call your name.
Please stand up, but do
remain by your seats, okay?
Um, Michelle Thomas.
Michelle Thomas?
Hi, Michelle.
Um, it says here, Michelle,
you're single, you're an attorney,
and it looks like your strengths
are history, mythology, and sports.
Um, I just want to ask you
one more thing, Michelle.
Why do you want to be a
contestant on our show?
Well, to learn things.
You know, about myself under
pressure, about other people.
But mostly because it would
just be so much gosh-darn fun.
Have a seat, Miss Thomas.
Uh, okay, Mr. Edward Price?
Miss Summers?
Miss Summers.
- Hi.
I'm Ben Matlock,
Dennis Blake's lawyer.
Miss Summers is busy.
Oh, no, no, no. That's okay.
Dennis is a friend of mine.
You're his lawyer, you're
a friend of mine, too.
Well, could we... I mean,
would it be all right if we talked?
Sure.
Could we... Could
we slow down a little?
How's this?
Wonderful.
You go ahead.
I'll catch up to you.
Ben here will protect me if
the need arises, won't you Ben?
Yeah.
I'll give it my best shot.
Well?
Well.
You have the prettiest smile.
You're sweet.
No, it's wonderful.
I bet you get offers to do
toothpaste commercials all the time.
Actually, I get
all kinds of offers.
Oh, I bet you do.
Oh, now, no, I meant...
But I'm under contract
to It's About Time.
You can't do anything else?
Well, Larry always said being underexposed
is far better than being overexposed.
Oh, so... Oh, you
and Larry were close?
Symbiotic is more
how I describe it.
I used...
I used Larry to get what I wanted,
and he used me to get what he wanted.
We were both very happy.
So it was just business?
Just business.
Ben, I can feel my gastrocnemius
muscles tightening up.
- You can?
- Yeah.
I really should
pick up the pace.
Oh, sure, sure.
I wouldn't want anything to happen
to your "gastrocnemic" muscles,
whatever they are.
My calf muscles. I
learned that on the show.
Aha.
See you.
Yeah. See you.
What can I tell
you? I hated him.
But he was your brother.
So? He was still a slime bucket.
Dennis said he was the
only one you ever worked for.
He produced some of the most
successful game shows on television,
and I wanted to
see how he did it.
In case you ever had to
step into his shoes, like now?
In case I ever felt like creating
and producing my own show.
Will you excuse me?
- Hello, people.
- Hi.
I'm Norm Fisher.
I'm Executive Producer
and at least temporarily the
Director of It's About Time as well.
Now, as I'm sure
Marge has explained,
you're about to play a mock
game of It's About Time.
Now, your performance
will be videotaped,
and reviewed by Marge and myself
before we make our final decision.
Remember, television
is a visual medium.
We'll be looking for bounce
and energy, enthusiasm.
A binga, bangada, boomada!
Now, who really wants to be a
contestant on It's About Time?
- I do! I do!
- I do!
I'd love to!
All right. Let's get out in front
of those cameras and prove it!
Before we tape our next trio, we're
going to take a ten-minute break.
Feel free to stand up, stretch your
legs, but please be back by 10:25.
Sure, no problem.
Oh, you startled me.
What are you doing?
I was just looking for
a soft drink machine.
Oh, gosh, I'm so excited,
I must have just missed it.
I'll see you inside.
Okay, people. Here's
the next question.
The first human heart
transplant operation
was performed by what
South African doctor?
- Rita.
- Debeggie?
No, that's incorrect. Michelle?
Christian Barnard.
Correct for $300.
Okay.
Jane Austin originally called this
famous novel First Impressions.
Under what title
was it published?
- Rita.
- Pride and Prejudice.
Correct for $200.
In a novel by Bram Stoker, "The
Hampstead Horror" is also known as?
- Michelle, it's yours.
- Dracula.
That's correct for $900.
Here's the final question.
What was the name of the
second man to set foot on the moon?
Take it Sheldon.
Neil Armstrong.
No, that's incorrect.
Michelle, it's yours.
Buzz Aldrin.
Right again, for $800.
All right, that'll do it.
And cut!
Well done, everyone.
Michelle, that's the highest anyone
has ever scored in a qualifying match.
Okay, you three can take
your seats, and let's have...
Well, there goes private
school for my kids.
You probably just
ruined their lives.
Congratulations.
Well, Mr. Fisher!
Mr. Matlock, what
are you doing here?
Well, to tell you the truth, my
investigator has been following you.
When he called and told me that
you were visiting Darryl Colburn,
I had to just see for myself.
Yeah, well, um, now is not
a good time for me. I'm busy.
Ah, Darryl Colburn was your
brother's biggest competition
in the game show
business. Wasn't he?
Yeah.
What were you
talking with him about?
Seems to me that's
none of your beeswax.
I just wondered if it
had anything to do
with that file you stole from
your brother's office this morning.
Look. You've got the wrong guy, babe.
I don't know what you're talking about.
The police don't like it when people
steal things from offices they've sealed,
especially when that office
is the scene of a murder.
Are you trying to accuse
me of stealing evidence?
You were seen in that office.
My brother had an idea
for a new game show.
So I figured I'd bring it to Darryl
Colburn while we were here in Atlanta.
No big deal.
Well, it belongs to me
anyway. I'm the sole heir.
Did Mr. Colburn buy it?
His lawyers are drawing
up the papers as we speak.
It's going to be bigger
than It's About Time.
The biggest game show ever.
You knew the idea.
Why'd you need the file?
I didn't know the idea.
Larry didn't give
me any details.
He didn't give the
details to anybody.
Sort of guarding
it with his life, huh?
Cute.
How's this?
Yeah, I think that's
going to look really good.
- Good length for you.
- Yeah.
Hello.
I was told to report here
to someone named Doreen.
Oh, yeah, that's me.
Come right on in, hon.
I'll be with you in a minute.
You're Kari Summers.
- Hi. You're a new contestant?
- Yeah. I just got the word.
- Well, congratulations.
- Thanks.
They seem to think I dress
like an insurance salesman.
Welcome to show biz, darling.
Oh, boy, what a fabulous dress.
- Hello.
- Thanks.
I'll tell the designer.
Is the designer
a friend of yours?
He likes to think he is.
- Hon, the phone's for you.
- Okay, thanks.
- All rightie, let's have a look at you.
- Hello.
Are you from Atlanta?
Are you crazy? What are
you doing calling me here?
My dear, think.
Honey, are you okay?
Oh, yeah.
Larry's dead. Things have
been nuts around here.
Bitten by a little dose
of stage fright, huh?
Yeah, I can see it a mile away.
Okay. Okay. I'll
do it right now.
You know, a little deep breathing right
before you go on usually does the trick.
Like this.
I'll call you at 5 and
tell you where it is.
And use your brain, will you?
- Don't call me here again.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry, Reeny, something has
come up, and I've really got to go.
Uh, I'll change in my
dressing room, okay?
Okay. Keep going.
Nice meeting you.
Would it be all right
if I use your phone?
Sure.
Are you feeling better?
Much.
Nikola Tesla.
Correct again, Walter.
Moving right along
to the next question,
who said, "That government
is best which governs least"?
You were first, Walter.
Thomas Jefferson.
Oh, I'm sorry. That's wrong.
Michelle at seven seconds.
Henry David Thoreau.
That is correct for $700,
and we have a new leader.
But we also have
one more question
which will determine which one of
you goes on to tonight's final countdown,
so listen very carefully.
He was 26 years
old, he was 3'7" tall,
and his name was Eddie Gaedel.
What professional
sport did he play?
Walter.
Baseball.
That is correct.
You've done it again, Walter.
Kari, would you please escort
Walter to the winner's circle?
And we will be right back
after this commercial message.
And cut.
Say goodbye to the other contestants
and set up for the final countdown.
Dennis, the big question
is on its way, babe.
Nice job, guys.
Go right over there.
Boy, you put
up a terrific fight.
Go over there.
Quiet, please. We're rolling.
Now, remember, Walter,
that for each full second remaining
on the clock, you will receive $1,000.
Are you ready for your
final countdown question?
I'm ready, Dennis.
Then let's go.
Former Chief Justice of the Supreme Court
John Marshall attended what law school?
Huh.
Harvard Law.
I'm sorry, Walter. I'm
afraid that's wrong.
John Marshall didn't
attend any law school.
Wait. Here.
Marge says Larry kept all the
questions and answers in his briefcase.
Well, let's see. His
briefcase is over there.
Let's see, the lights
in the studio went off.
The door opened.
He stabbed... and
then walked over here,
took the briefcase,
picked it up,
probably got out...
the answers... yeah.
Got a piece of paper
to jot them down, and...
Uh-oh.
- What?
- Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Look at that stationery.
So?
Yeah, but look at the masthead.
He'd only fired
Dennis the day before.
Proof.
We've been carrying it
around with us all day.
Kari, your smile could
make a sick man well.
Thank you.
But more than your smile and your
other attributes, you're educated.
- You have a college degree, don't you?
- That's right.
- From where?
- The University of Texas at Austin.
In what?
Communications,
television production.
Uh-huh. And before Larry Fisher
hired you, where were you working?
I was working with a floor crew
at a TV station in Milwaukee.
Mm-hmm. Did you ever do any
lighting while you were there?
Lots. I did it all.
So you were able to use
your off-screen knowledge
before Larry came along and
put you in front of the camera?
Right.
Did he sign you to
an exclusive contract?
Yes.
So you weren't allowed to do
any ads or commercials or movies
or other projects outside
of It's About Time?
If the project had
Larry's approval, I could.
Hmm.
Approximately how many
projects were you offered last year?
About a dozen or so.
Mm. And to how many
did Larry give his approval?
None.
Huh.
Well, if Larry had given his approval,
how much would you have made?
A few thousand dollars.
I really don't know.
Kari, you're the most popular
woman in daytime television to date.
Don't you think a couple of hundred
thousand would be closer to the truth?
Objection. The question
is argumentative,
and this whole line of
questioning is irrelevant.
The state believes
that my client is guilty
largely because he had
opportunity and motive, Your Honor.
How can this guy object
when I'm just trying to establish
that somebody else did, too?
Overruled.
This contract that he had you
sign, how much did you make?
Five hundred dollars a show.
Hmm. How many shows a year?
About 160 or so.
So you grossed... let
me... $80,000 a year.
That's right.
I bet that sounded like a lot
of money back in Milwaukee,
but now, as big a star as
you are, it's peanuts, isn't it?
No, I don't think so.
You never resented Larry for
locking you into a contract like that?
No.
But you did find a way to
make up for that extra income
that he had denied
you, didn't you?
I don't know what you mean.
You recognize this?
No.
Well, maybe you'll
recognize what's inside.
That is your
handwriting, isn't it, Kari?
And those are the
questions and answers
that were used on It's
About Time, aren't they?
You were selling
them to Walter Beltram.
We intercepted this envelope
that you left for him at the hotel,
and what he eventually got was
an envelope that we left for him.
That's why he lost.
We fed him the wrong answer.
He appreciates all the
money you helped him make,
but he's not appreciative
enough to commit perjury.
All right, it's true.
I saw an opportunity,
and I took it.
And Larry found out
about it, didn't he?
And that's what you and
he were arguing about
just before my client showed up.
You knew if he exposed you,
your career would be just about over,
so you attached a timing device to
the lighting board before the next show
so the lights would go
out during the taping.
And when they went out,
nobody could see anything.
You left the stage and went to
Larry's office and stabbed him
with something that would
look like my client had done it.
But then you saw his briefcase,
and you couldn't help yourself.
You grabbed a pencil
and a piece of paper,
and you scratched out the
questions and the answers
that Larry kept in his briefcase
one more time, didn't you?
That's not true. I
didn't do any of that.
I... I wasn't even in
his office that day.
I wrote down those questions
and answers a week ago.
No. No.
And this stationery proves it.
Look, It's About Time.
And look at the masthead...
Starring Lance McCormick.
Larry moved fast, didn't he?
The same day he fired Dennis,
he ordered new stationery
with his new star's
name on the masthead.
And, according to the
records at the print shop,
they delivered this stationery just
moments before the lights went out.
The only time you could have written
down these questions and these answers
was after Larry was dead.
Kari, I'm... I'm sorry to have done
all this to a person as pretty as you,
with that smile, but I had to.
- Oh, please sign mine.
- I'm so glad...
Happy guy.
I've got you two
to thank for it.
You wouldn't say that if you
knew how close I came to blowing it.
- Blowing what?
- That stupid game show.
I came this close to hitting my
buzzer on that Gaedel question.
It was a reflex.
If I hadn't stopped myself,
we'd never have known for sure
Walter and Kari were in cahoots.
You knew the answer?
Of course.
Eddie Gaedel came to bat once
in 1951 for the St. Louis Browns
and walked on
four straight pitches.
You guys didn't know that?
www.tvsubtitles.net